Inaban...
I thought you were a goner.
I'm not gonna die from
a little dizzy spell.
Still, I was so scared.
I thought he might be responsible.
This has nothing to do with Heartseed.
I've been feeling a little
under the weather.
Nothing I would have gone
to the nurse's office for.
Don't say that, Inaba-chan.
You need to take care of your own body.
Are you actually scolding me?
I really mean it!
Yeah, whatever you say.
This shouldn't have to
be such a big deal.
I can walk home by myself.
If we don't walk you home,
Kiriyama will give us
a hard kick tomorrow.
Yup, since Yui and Aoki
wanted to tag along.
Screw that.
I don't need four people
escorting me around.
So, Taichi...
Why don't you tell us what really
happened with Yui yesterday?
What kind of question is that?
That came out of nowhere.
Who cares?
If you don't answer the question,
I'll be so upset that I'll
collapse on the spot.
It's not fair to use your
poor health as an excuse.
I think I'm gonna faint from the shock.
Huh?
You really have so little trust in us?
Sob.
Right, Inaban?
Yeah.
Fine, fine.
But I can't tell you
anything that's private.
How did you come up with that
brilliant idea, selfless freak?
It's not that funny.
So does it still hurt down there?
That's none of your business.
Help me out here, Nagase.
What's wrong?
I had no idea.
I knew that Yui didn't like boys,
but I never realized that she
was actually scared of them.
Nagase, I'm pretty sure that Kiriyama
didn't want people to feel uncomfortable
or start tiptoeing around her.
So try to act normal around her.
Act normal...
That's all I have to do?
Yeah, that's enough.
You two would make the perfect couple
since you need each other.
I guarantee it.
I-Inaban!
Don't decide things like that on your own!
The other day, you were saying
how Taichi and I were all...
...wooga wooga and stuff!
Huh?
That's because you guys
are all wooga wooga.
Plus, I have a feeling that Yui's
starting to fall for Taichi.
Wh-What?!
Inaban, you're too frank.
The problem with selfless freaks
is that they tend to make girls swoon.
Never forget that kindness
can hurt instead of help.
I understand.
Sorry about everything today.
Don't sweat it.
Get some rest.
Inaban, you should be worried more about
your own health than about everyone else.
I'm okay.
Oh, that's right.
I almost forgot.
Iori, you should have
Taichi cure your trauma, too.
Huh?
Inaban, you promised not to tell anyone.
Taichi, I have faith in you.
Help her out.
Inaban decides everything on her own.
It's too much.
I mean, I know that
she's trying to help...
Do you want to know
more about me, Taichi?
Well...
I'm willing to talk if you promise
that nothing will change,
no matter what I say.
Okay, I promise.
I knew you would say that.
Well, I'll start then.
Yeah...
But first...
I'll tell a joke.
Huh?
Well, I always think it's a good idea
to say something funny before
the mood gets serious.
Don't bother.
Why would you think that?
But when I really need to,
I can never think of anything funny!
All the more reason to not do it.
Just kidding.
The joke was that I couldn't come up
with a joke when I needed one.
But I actually do have a joke.
I just chose to joke that I
didn't have a joke, got it?
What is there to get?
You didn't need to joke that
you didn't have a joke,
because you didn't need to
joke in the first place.
But you're actually
playing along, Taichi.
That seems to happen
when I'm around you.
So, I have five dads.
But I guess only three
of them were official.
Do you mean that your
mother keeps getting
divorced and remarried?
Yup, and my second dad was trouble.
Let's just say that he could be violent.
But nothing serious happened
because I made sure of it.
I learned to adopt a persona.
One that fit his preferences.
What do you—
I was careful not to do anything
that would make him angry.
If I behaved like this or did that,
he wouldn't get mad.
He might even praise me.
I changed my tastes to match.
This was back when I was
in first grade, I think.
Ever since, I've been
switching between personas.
But in spring of last year,
my fifth dad told me
this on his deathbed:
"You need to start
living your own life."
And after he died,
my mom said, "I'm sorry
for being so selfish.
From now on, I'll work hard so
you can do the things you want,"
while crying her eyes out.
And we lived happily ever after.
So you get along with your mom?
But the real hell starts after that.
Live your own life.
Those words left me stunned.
What did I like?
What did I want to do?
After spending most of my life trying
to live as someone else wanted,
I'd apparently forgotten who I was.
My mom told me to do what I wanted,
but I didn't know what that was.
So I decided to just pick appropriate
personas based on the situation.
Ironically enough, I prided myself on
being able to guess what
other people wanted.
But I've started to lose my touch.
I never realized that
Yui had androphobia.
But that's...
And then, this personality
swapping business started.
I barely had a grip on my
personality as it was.
Once we began switching
bodies, it only got worse.
Eventually, nobody will be
able to recognize me.
I won't be able to recognize myself.
Then maybe, eventually,
I'll just fade away...
That will never happen!
Because no matter what happens,
no matter how much you change,
I'll always be able to recognize
you for who you are.
That's impossible.
It's not impossible.
How can you be so sure?
That's because...
I'm in love with...
Selfless freak.
A-Anyway, I'll be able to recognize you.
You can trust me.
Really?
If you're that confident,
I guess I can trust you.
Morning, Taichi.
M-Morning, Nagase.
You swore that I could spill my guts
and nothing would change!
You promised me, man to man!
Who are you supposed to be?
You swore that I could spill my
guts and nothing would change!
You promised me, man to man!
Why are you repeating yourself?
And you're not a man.
So why is it that when two guys talk,
there's so much adrenaline involved?
Hell if I know.
Anyway, are you okay?
Yup, I'm fine.
But that question should probably
be directed at someone else.
Are you me right now, Taichi?
Taichi! Are you okay, Taichi?
Just suck it up.
You're such a wimp.
I don't think I can suck it all back up.
Iori, you can go back to the classroom.
What about you guys?
I'll make sure he gets some rest.
Don't worry.
I'm not going to hurt my own body.
I'm back.
Looks like it.
You can go back to the classroom.
I'm not going to leave you
all alone while you're sick.
Sorry.
No, don't be.
You've been acting strangely lately.
I'm telling you that I'm fine.
You don't look fine to me.
Tell me what's wrong.
Keep it down.
You're giving me a headache.
Inaba!
I want to help you!
Why do you want to help me?
B-Because...
Don't say that it's because you
want to help or because I'm one of you.
Well, you're always looking out for us.
You're always there
for us when it counts.
So if I didn't look out for you,
you wouldn't want to help me?
Not exactly...
That was kind of a mean way to put it.
It wasn't mean.
Why do you guys have to be so nice?
Why couldn't you be a little darker?
Darker?
No, I shouldn't say that.
I'm the one who needs to change.
Uh, Inaba...
Are you sure you're okay?
What are you asking about?
My body will be fine
after a little rest.
I'm not talking about your body.
I'm not okay!
Wait.
I didn't mean that. Forget what I said.
Seriously?
I meant to say that—
You once said that we were
in a hopeless situation.
Aren't you the one who's hurting the most
because of this swapping business?
Crap.
I'm in horrible shape today.
Looking weak in front of an enemy.
You said something
similar the other day.
Am I your enemy?
No!
That's not what I meant!
You guys are
my very best friends.
Which makes you my worst enemies.
That makes no...
I'm done talking.
Go back to the classroom.
If you can't tell us why
you're in so much pain,
you don't think of us as friends.
Then I'll give it to you straight.
I can't trust you guys.
If two people switch bodies,
and one commits a crime or something,
the owner of that body is
the one who's responsible.
That means you can do whatever you want.
You think we would do that?
Well, it may be unfair to say
you'd commit a crime.
But you could swipe some
change or something.
I guess, but...
I can't help but think about the
bad things you might be doing.
It's so scary that it
keeps me up all night.
What's sad is that
I hate my own guts for being like this.
You, Iori, Yui, and Aoki
all trust each other.
I'm the only one who's
worrying about this stuff.
Inaba...
We won't think less of you for it—
But this completely changes
our relationship, right?
Taichi...
I don't trust anybody in this world.
That means everyone is an enemy.
And you're probably my worst enemy
since unless I'm mistaken,
you trust me more than anyone else does.
I say that I don't trust anybody,
but I still want to
have fun with everyone.
That indecision is making
every day pure agony for me.
I don't suffer from any trauma
the way Yui and Iori do.
A lot of people end up
with warped personalities
after going through some
crazy life experiences.
If you ask me, they're better off,
since trauma can be cured.
But what are you supposed to
do when there is no trauma?
I haven't been able to trust anyone
since the day I was born.
If I try to change,
I won't be the same person anymore.
Won't be the same person anymore...
In that sense,
you're probably doomed to
be a selfless freak forever.
Were you born that way?
Yeah, you can't help people who
don't suffer from any trauma.
But that's probably because
they don't need help.
It really doesn't matter
what you're born with.
Are you saying that it would
be stupid to worry about that?
I didn't say that.
But I guess that you're probably right.
Taichi!
I mean, I think you're
fine the way you are.
Huh?
I'll admit that I'm sad
you don't trust me,
but that doesn't mean you should
force yourself to change.
I think everyone will still accept you.
Nagase, Kiriyama, Aoki,
and of course, me.
Are you stupid?!
It's not that simple!
We can't say that for sure.
So you should talk to everyone.
Tell them what you told me.
I can't take that risk!
What if they don't accept me—
In that case, you'll still have me.
Anyway, you need to start
by accepting who you are.
In my opinion.
I-I can't do it.
The only consequences I can
imagine are all negative.
Hey, Inaba.
When you're hiding a secret
from the whole world,
it puts a weight on your shoulders.
So I'm going to tell you
a secret that I was planning
to take to the grave.
What do you mean?
You spill yours, so I have to spill mine?
Yeah.
If my secret gets out,
I won't be able to
survive in this school,
or in normal society, for that matter.
This is a lethal secret I'm hiding.
Are you insane or something?!
Inaba, y-you're too loud!
Whatever, just tell me
this secret of yours.
I'll decide after that.
Okay, here I go...
I've...
I've masturbated to you before!
You mean that you've actually...
Yeah.
Which probably means you've
also used Iori and Yui, right?
Yeah.
I see.
I-I want to make it clear that
this isn't a regular thing!
I've hardly done it at all, actually!
Are you listening to me?
Perv!
Pervert!
Sicko! Freak! Creep! Scum! Animal!
Still...
I think you're fine the way you are.
Huh?
This is all so stupid.
It's stupid that you revealed
this secret to me!
That you thought it would
convince me to change my mind!
It's stupid that you thought it was
acceptable to say that out loud.
And what's really stupid is
that I'm actually touched.
Need a handkerchief?
What's wrong with you?
You want me to fall for you too?
That's more or less it.
So Inaban, you're saying that...
...you worry too much?
W-Worry too much?
It's a lot more than—
I know what you mean.
Whenever Aoki and I switch,
I give my body a thorough
check as soon as I'm back.
What?
And I make sure that none
of my stuff is missing.
That hurt! That really hurt!
And it's only when you switch with me?!
What about Taichi?!
Um, that's all you have to say?
Well, you kind of went overboard,
thinking that we would commit crimes.
But don't worry.
I won't use your body
to do anything bad.
Wait, Inaba-chan. You're saying that
you don't trust any of us, right?
It's not just me, right?
That's what you're worried about?!
Anyway, let's eat.
Lunch is going to end soon.
Yeah, we can talk while we eat.
What the...
Why was I ever worried?
I made a fool out of
myself for nothing.
Hey, I've never done anything bad
while I was in your body, Yui.
Whatever, I know your secret now.
I can't trust you.
Inaba, could you forget what I sa—
Weren't you making creepy movies
with Taichi the other day?
No way.
That's the only exception!
In return, I'll tell you my secret.
What's she talking about?!
What creepy movies?!
Then we're in the same boat.
I've also masturbated to you before.
What?!
That's a gentle way of going insane.
I fell in love with you,
and that hasn't changed.
So how do you feel about Iori, Taichi?
You're just a selfish freak!
Is that so wrong?!
Nagase!